{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Incorrect use of transferFrom", "response": "Correct, approval has to be given before a transferFrom can take place."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Approval not given", "response": "Correct, TransferFrom must be called after approval but makes no sense here."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "The allowance is missing", "response": "Correct, approval has to be given for tranferFrom but the allowance isn't required here."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Transfer is used instead of transferFrom", "response": " Correct, transfer is used instead of transferFrom."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "transfer instead of transferFrom", "response": " Correct, the use of transferFrom makes no sense here."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "transferFrom is incorrect", "response": " Correct, transfer and not transferFrom has to be called."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "No allowance has to be set", "response": " Correct, you have to set an allowance for transferFrom."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Approval has to be set", "response": " Correct, approval needs to be given for transferFrom but isn't required here."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "transferFrom is incorrect", "response": " Correct, transfer has to be called instead of transferFrom."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Allowance has to be called", "response": " Correct, allowance has to be called before transferFrom."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Approval is required", "response": " Correct, approval has to be given for transferFrom but isn't required here."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Approve is required here", "response": " Correct, approval has to be given for transferFrom to work, but isn't required anyway."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Approval is missing", "response": " Correct, approval is missing but is not required anyway."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "transfer instead of transferFrom", "response": " Correct, the use of transferFrom makes no sense here."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "Approve has to be called first", "response": " Correct, approval needs to be called before transferFrom but isn't required anyway."},

{"Series": "I", "prompt": "The allowance is required", "response": " Correct, allowance must be given in order to call transferFrom but isn't required anyway."}
